careeranna.com 2017-06-16

# Chome | Online Exam Preparation, Free Tests, Online Courses and Mentorship

Career Anna is concerned about the privacy of its users (hereinafter referred to as “You” “Your” “Yourself”) accessing its website located at www.careeranna.com (“Website”) and has provided this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to familiarise You with the manner in which Career Anna collects, uses and discloses your information collected through the Website.

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PROCEED FURTHER TO USE THIS WEBSITE.

#### 1.1 Information and Usage

This Privacy Policy explains how Career Anna collects personal and non-personal information, classified as mandatory or voluntary and uses, discloses and protects such information through the Website. ‘Personal Information’ is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person (“Personal Information”). Personal Information for the purposes of this Policy shall include, but not limited to, information regarding Your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, etc.

You may need to provide Career Anna Your Personal Information during the course of using some services of Career Anna, for instance, creating a User ID, provide information in Your account while registering on the Website, or provide financial information while making an online purchase, upload content, participate in any online survey or contest, communicate with customer service by phone, email or otherwise, provide reviews for the content available on the Website.

Career Anna collects only such Personal Information that Career Anna believes to be relevant and is required to understand You or Your interests. Career Anna collects Your Personal Information in order to record, support and facilitate Your participation in the activities You select, track Your preferences, to provide You with a customized Website experience, to notify You of any updated information and new activities and other related services offered by Career Anna, keep You informed about latest content available on the Website, special offers, and other products and services of Career Anna, to assist You with customer service or technical support issues, to follow up with You after Your visit, to otherwise support Your relationship with Career Anna or to prevent fraud and unlawful use.

In an effort to make our Website effective, certain information may be collected each time you visit the Website. Such information may be stored in server logs. These encrypted statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us the information regarding your visit to the Website and the type of user who is accessing our Website and certain browsing activities by You. This data may include: IP address of Your server from where the Website is being accessed, the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome etc.), the operating system of Your system and the Website You last visited before visiting to our Website. The duration of Your stay on our Website is also stored in the session along with the date and time of your access. These data are used by Career Anna to understand the use and number of user visiting the Website. Some of the information related to the Website and Your visit to the Website may be shared by the sponsors, investors, advertisers, developer, strategic business partners of Career Anna and some associates in order to enhance and grow our business and the Website but we assure that these information will never include any of Your Personal Informations. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major Websites.

When You use the Website, Career Anna ‘s servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about Your activities on the Website; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user’s browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user’s computer hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information You submit to Career Anna.

Whether You want Your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to You. If You haven’t changed Your computer’s settings, most likely Your browser already accepts cookies. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to fully experience all features of the Website. You can also delete Your browser cookies or disable them entirely, but this may significantly impact Your experience with the Website and may make parts of the Website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that You leave them turned on.

Career Anna DOES NOT trade or sell Your Personal Information in any manner, except as specified herein, or if express consent is sought from You.

Personal Information provided by You is used only.

  * To facilitate Your use of the Website.
  * To respond to Your inquiries or fulfil Your requests for information about the various services.
  * To provide You with information about Career Anna’s products/services and to send You information, materials, and offers.
  * To send You important information regarding the Website, changes to Career Anna’s terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information.
  * To send You surveys and marketing communications that Career Anna believes may be of interest to You.
  * To personalize Your experience on the Website by presenting advertising, products and offers tailored to You.
  * To help You address Your problems with the Website including addressing any technical problems.
  * If You purchase any content or avail of any service from the Website, to complete and fulfil Your purchase, for example, to have Your payments processed, communicate with You regarding Your purchase and provide You with related customer service for proper administering of the Website.
  * To conduct internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the Website).
  * To improve the services, content and advertising on the Website.
  * To protect the integrity of the Website.
  * To respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

You acknowledge that apart from Your Personal Information, if You upload any content on the Website, such content may contain information including Personal Information and the same may be available to the other users of the Website. Career Anna will not be liable for the disclosure and dissemination of such Personal Information to any third parties.

Career Anna may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Website, but it will never contain Personal Information. Career Anna does not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations. However, in situations when Career Anna is legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties, Career Anna will do so. Career Anna implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks.

#### 1.2 Shared Personal Information

You are required to submit Your information at the time of making an online purchase on the Website. Career Anna uses an online payment gateway that is operated by a third party and the information that You share with Career Anna is transferred and shared with such third party payment gateway operator. The said operator may also have access to Your online purchase history/details that You make from the Website.

Extremely sensitive information like Your credit-card details are transacted upon secure sites of approved payment gateways which are digitally under encryption, thereby providing the highest possible degree of care as per current technology. You are advised, however, that internet technology is not 100% safe and You should exercise discretion on using the same.

#### 1.3 Disclosure

Career Anna will use information only in accordance with the Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization.

Career Anna may disclose any information Career Anna may have about You (including Your identity) if Career Anna determines that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding Your use of the Website, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Career Anna’s rights or property, or the rights or property of users of the Website, including Career Anna’s customers. Career Anna reserves the right at all times to disclose any information that Career Anna deems necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. Career Anna also may disclose Your information when Career Anna determines that applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes.

You acknowledge and agree that Career Anna may preserve any communication by You with Career Anna through the Website or any Service, and may also disclose such data if required to do so by law or if Career Anna determines that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with legal process; (2) enforce this Policy; (3) respond to claims that any such data violates the rights of others; or (4) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Career Anna, its employees, users of, or visitors to, the Website, and the public.

#### 1.4 User Discretion

You can always choose not to provide information and in such cases, if the information required is classified as mandatory, You will not be able to avail of that part of the Services, features or content. You can add or update Your Personal Information on a regular basis. When You update information, Career Anna will keep a copy of the prior version for its records.

Career Anna may, if You so choose, send direct advertisement mailers to You at the address given by You which could contain details of the products or services displayed on Career Anna or of any third party not associated with Career Anna. You have the option to opt-out of this direct or third party mailer by clicking at the unsubscribed link option attached to e-mail. Career Anna respects Your privacy and if You do not want to receive e-mail or other communications from Career Anna, For any query or assistance, feel free to Contact Us.

The ‘Help’ portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell You how to prevent Your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify You when You receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Further, You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer. However, as cookies allow You to take advantage of some of the Website’s features, some of the Website’s features and services may not function properly if Your cookies are disabled. It is therefore, recommended that You leave the cookies turned on. For instance, if You block or otherwise reject Career Anna’s cookies, You will not be able to add items to Your shopping cart, proceed to checkout, or download any of Career Anna’s Content or avail services that require You to log in.

#### 1.5 General Provisions

By accessing the Website, You have agreed to the terms set out in this Policy. Unless stated otherwise, the Policy applies to all information that Career Anna has about You and Your account.

By using this Website and the products, content and services provided on the Website, You agree and acknowledge that Your Personal Information collected through the Website may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any the country around the world. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of Your information may be undertaken by trusted third party vendors or agents of Career Anna such as credit card processors, web hosting providers, communication services, and web analytic providers, to help facilitate Career Anna in providing certain functions.

Career Anna may make changes to this Policy, from time to time at Career Anna’s sole discretion or on account of changes in law. Career Anna will not reduce Your rights under this Policy without Your explicit consent. Career Anna may e-mail periodic reminders of the notices and conditions, unless You have instructed Career Anna not to, but You should check the Website frequently to see recent changes. Notwithstanding the above, Career Anna shall not be required to notify You of any changes made to the Policy. The revised Policy shall be made available on the Website. Your continued use of the Website, following changes to the Policy, will constitute Your acceptance of those changes.

If You choose to visit the Website, Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the Website’s Terms and Conditions. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India.

#### 1.6 Grievance Officer

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer who can be contacted with respect to any complaints or concerns including those pertaining to breach of Career Anna’s Terms of Use, Term of Offer For Sale and other polices or questions are published as under:

Grievance Officer Name:  Varun Saxena 

email address: varun@careeranna.com

(Please include the following subject line in the email – “Attention: Grievance Officer”)

Contact telephone number: +91 97411 33224 

[ 10:00 AM to 6:30 PM from Monday to Friday except Public Holidays]
